(Penny:)What are you talking about?
(Leonard:)You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
(Bernadette:)No, she doesn't.
I just made that up.
(Leonard:)Why would you do that?
(Bernadette:)Because you were about to quit like
a big-- Sheldon, cover your ears.
(Sheldon:)I'm not a child.
I know the word "ninny."
(Penny:)Yeah, well, you should have quit
'cause I'm still gonna beat your ass.
(Bernadette:)Wish I had a man
like her on my team.
(Leonard:)Hey, I am every bit
as much of a man as Penny.
Now, Iet's do this!
Walt, it's not all pants,
there's one shirt.
(Leonard:)-Oh.
-Hey, that's my shirt.
(Leonard:)-This one is, too.
-No, no, that's not mine.
-That has a big spot on it.
-Wait. So does this one.
(Bernadette:)Maybe the spot's the clue.
"Sheldon's spot."
The coin is in your spot!
(Sheldon:)-Oh, that's clever.
Hurry!
(Sheldon:)Be there in a minute.
I just have to pre-soak these!